My name is Geoffrey Okwengu.
I came all the way from Kenya.
The first time I came,
the problem that brought me here was HIV 1 and 2.
For how many years were you having this problem of HIV?
I had suffered for two years.
I discovered I was HIV positive when I was about to get married.
That is how the plans for marriage disappeared.
I was always getting sick.
That was why I decided to come to The SCOAN to be prayed for so that I would be healed.
Before you came, when you discovered that you were positive to HIV,
how did you feel?
I felt very sad and bad because I knew the enemy had me.
I was destined for the grave at a very early age.
I tested positive at Nairobi Hospital.
So I came here and the man of God prayed for me.
I was given the Morning Water and I went home.
I kept administering it.
After a while, I had a dream.
I had an encounter with the man of God, Prophet T.B. Joshua, in a dream
where he appeared to me.
It was in a theatre; he was operating on me.
After he had finished, he told me, "You are healed".
In the dream I said, "Thank You, Jesus. I'm healed".
Then I woke up from the dream.
Immediately after that, I found out that I was now getting better.
I was feeling okay; I was feeling good.
Then I went for a test.
I then discovered that I was HIV negative.
Shall we put our hands together for our Lord Jesus!
This is somebody who was given a certificate of death,
meaning someone who was tested HIV 1 and 2.
The man of God prayed for him in the midst of the crowd.
Can you tell us the name of the hospital that tested you right now negative.
It was Nairobi Hospital.
The same hospital?
Yes.
That once tested you positive?
And you went back and now you are negative?
Yes.
Wow. Can you tell us - what happened after the man of God prayed for you?
I am totally free.
I was able to get married.
My marriage got delayed. Even my younger siblings - I'm the first born - got married before me.
I now got married; I had a very big wedding in 2013.
Now I have two boys.
Mr Geoffrey Okwengu
Morning Water Testimony
Brother, what were the symptoms you were having,
apart from the medical report we are seeing right now?
What were the symptoms you were having then that you are no longer having right now?
I was having very high fever.
I was sweating when I was sleeping.
I was losing weight
I became very thin; thinner than I am right now.
All of those symptoms disappeared.
I am no longer having them; I am okay.
The advice I will give to those having a similar problem is
that there is no disease Jesus cannot heal.
In this place, the Lord is able to heal every kind of disease.
Make your way here and the Lord is going to touch you and heal you.
Amen. We believe with you and know that Jesus Christ healed
and He still heals all manner of sickness and disease.
If Jesus Christ in His infinite mercy can use His able servant Prophet T.B. Joshua to heal you
from this problem of HIV/Aids, we believe He can do it for anyone
who is also listening to you to the glory of God.
Once again, let us put our hands together for Christ Jesus!
This one on top are the results that showed that I was HIV positive.
They date back to 2010.
The first one here is the one that confirmed it.
This other one is a lab report, and this one was for confirmation that I was HIV positive.
This ones down here are very recent reports -
a lab report showing that I am HIV negative and a confirmation report showing the same.
Mr Geoffrey Okwengu
Morning Water Testimony
The picture down here:
this one is my wife,
this is me,
and our wonderful two children.
I named my first born Joshua
because of what the Lord did for me when I came here.
His name is Joshua.
The second born is Elijah.
He is 2 1/2 years old, and the other one - his birthday is on June 20th.
My children are all clean; they are all HIV negative and okay.
Hallelujah! Once again, let us put our hands together for Christ Jesus!
We thank God for your life. We rejoice with you.
We want to remind you that the reason why you were healed
is for you to serve Christ Jesus for the rest of your life.
Make His Word the standard for your life,
continue to be loyal to Him and train your children in the way of the Lord
so that when they grow up, they will not depart from it, in Jesus' name.
Once again, let us put our hands together for Christ Jesus!